maxhealthcare.in 2019-12-08

# Privacy Policy | Max Hospital

## Get Second Opinion

Name *

Email *

Phone*

Country Code *

Please enter 10 digit mobile number *

Please provide your phone number with country code

Hospital Network *

## Doc Connect

Hospital : 

Max Super Speciality Hospital, Saket

Description: 

  * Robotic Urological Surgery: 15 years journey   
Dr. Rahul Yadav, Dr. Anant Kumar
  * Robotic surgery is the latest in advanced onco surgical procedures   
Dr. Harit Chaturvedi
  * Percutaneous balloon aortic valvuloplasty & balloon dilatation of aortic coarctation in a 10 year old child   
Dr. Neeraj Awasthy, Dr. Sushil Shukla
  * Role of CT/MR imaging and echocardiography in evaluation of valsalva sinus aneurysm   
Dr. Reena Anand, Dr. Raj Kumar, Dr. Divya Malhotra, Dr. Bharat Aggarwal
  * Risk factors for patients undergoing treatment for Breast Cancer  
Ms. Kanika Arora, Ms. Ritika Samaddar
  * Radiology Case of The Month   
Dr. Nafisa Shakir Batta, Dr. Dhruv Jain

### Bio Medical Waste Report For Shalimar Bagh

Month | Red Autoclave(Infected Plastic Waste) | Yellow- Incineration(AnatomicalWaste & Soiled Waste) | Blue Autoclave (Glass- Bottles) | Black Cytotoxic- Incineration( Cytotoxic Contaminated Items) | White- Sharp | Total Bags | Total Weight(In KG's)  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
  | No. of Bags | Weight (in KG's) | No. of Bags | Weight (in KG's) | No. of Bags | Weight (in KG's) | No. of Bags | Weight (in KG's) | No. of Bags | Weight (in KG's) |   |    
Apr-17 | 924 | 2963.50 | 954 | 2994.10 | 239 | 1017.30 | 103 | 279.20 | 1645 | 606.40 | 3865 | 7861.00  
May-17 | 1175 | 4624.12 | 1028 | 3498.40 | 276 | 1524.34 | 87 | 195.01 | 1803 | 823.85 | 4369 | 10665.71  
Jun-17 | 1060 | 4511.45 | 902 | 2886.66 | 293 | 1324.05 | 76 | 194.00 | 2057 | 1100.69 | 4388 | 10016.85  
Jul-17 |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   | 0 | 0.00  
Aug-17 |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   | 0 | 0.00  
Sep-17 |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   | 0 | 0.00  
Oct-17 |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   | 0 | 0.00  
Nov-17 |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   | 0 | 0.00  
Dec-17 |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   | 0 | 0.00  
Jan-18 |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   | 0 | 0.00  
Feb-18 |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   | 0 | 0.00  
Mar-18 |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   | 0 | 0.00  
YTD | 3159 | 12099.065 | 2884 | 9379.155 | 808 | 3865.69 | 266 | 668.705 | 5505 | 2530.94 | 12622 | 28543.555  
  
  1. Home

#### Clinical Directorate

### Clinical Excellence Reports

For more info please call 8744 888 888 (Delhi – NCR) & 9988 422 333 (Chandigarh Tri-city), or mail at [homecare@maxhealthcare.com](mailto:%20homecare@maxhealthcare.com)

Maxhealthcare.in is committed to protecting your privacy. It is important to us that our customers retain their privacy while taking advantage of the services that we have to offer. To this end, we adhere to the following basic principles:

We employ the highest levels of security to keep your personal information strictly confidential.

We will not disclose or sell any of your personal information, including your name, address, age, sex or medical history to any third party without your permission.

Although we use cookie technology to help users navigate our site efficiently we never use cookies to store personal information, such as credit card numbers. Please be aware, however, that our site contains link to other sites and that the privacy practices of other sites may differ from those of maxhealthcare.in. If you have any additional questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies, please email us at [privacy@maxhealthcare.com](mailto:privacy@maxhealthcare.com) and we'll respond within 24 hours.

**Our Privacy Policy explains:**

  * What information we collect from you
  * How we use that information

Your privacy is of utmost importance to us. If you have any questions you can reach out to us at <[digitalquery@maxhealthcare.com](mailto:digitalquery@maxhealthcare.com)>

**Information we collect**

We collect information to provide better services to you, and we may send this information to third party tools to improve our services, and to personalise your app experience.

We collect information in the following ways:

  * Information you give us: Name, phone number, email id <<this section depends on the information that is being collected by your application>>
  * Information we automatically collect:  
    * Device & Hardware information - We collect device-specific information such as device make & model, network information, advertiser ID (to uniquely identify your device) and email address, if available 
    * Location information - We automatically capture your public IP address, and your geo coordinates   << for android apps, if the location permission is available, lat/long is automatically collected>>

**How we use information we collect**

We use this data and may send it to a third party tools for analytics so that we can personalize your app experience
